<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hudson Worden</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Hudson Worden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hworden.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building Poker Part 1</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/building-poker-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/building-poker-1/</guid><description>Introduction What inspired me to start this journey was recently being tasked with finding a &amp;ldquo;Casino / Poker night&amp;rdquo; online as a team celebration activity. I felt like there was a gap in the casual and Zoom oriented niche.
Ever since COVID, people have been looking for new ways to interact with one another in socially distant ways. There has been an emergence of social games that can be played in the browser, with the User Experience centered around Zoom / Video Calling.</description></item><item><title>Automating Building in Public</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/automating-building-in-public/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/automating-building-in-public/</guid><description>Introduction As I mentioned in my previous post, I have begun building my personal site to post projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been learning about &amp;ldquo;Building in Public&amp;rdquo; and central to it is to maintain constant communication with the public. I thought that it would be great if I could post links to my personal site on Twitter. That way my followers could instantly see any new updates I&amp;rsquo;ve made.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/about/</guid><description>My name is Hudson Worden and I&amp;rsquo;m currently a Software Engineer for a Silicon Valley Tech Giant. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working professionally as a Software Engineer since 2016, but have been a hobbyist programmer since 2011.
During my tenure at my current employer, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked my way up from an Associate Software Engineer all the way to Lead Software Engineer.
I hold formal education in Computer Science:
Ms of Computer Science Georgia Tech (2017 - 2021) Spec.</description></item><item><title>My New Site</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/my-new-site/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/my-new-site/</guid><description>Intro Hi everyone, this is my first post on my new site. So welcome! I was able to build this site in less than an hour using Hugo.
Hugo Summary For those who may not know, Hugo is a static site generator. You can store your site content in markdown files, and then apply either a custom or open source theme to your site. Hugo will then take the content files, and translate them to equivalent html pages.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Hey there! My working hours are 9 - 5 EST.
Feel free to reach out to hudson.worden@gmail.com. Thanks!</description></item></channel></rss>