<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Hudson Worden</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Hudson Worden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hworden.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building Poker Part 2</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/building-poker-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/building-poker-2/</guid><description>Introduction In my previous post my next goal was to implement state management into the app thus far. Previously, I was using hard coded values scattered within various files and it was quickly becoming difficult to manage.
Enter Redux React projects typically use React Redux for state management. React Redux is the official React binding library for Redux. Redux in it of itself is a library for state management.</description></item><item><title>Building Poker Part 1</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/building-poker-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/building-poker-1/</guid><description>Introduction Ever since COVID, people have been looking for new ways to interact with one another in socially distant ways. There has been an emergence of social games that can be played in the browser, with the User Experience centered around Zoom / Video Calling. Two examples of this are Jack Box and Codenames. The end goal is to basically make a similar experience, but for Poker.</description></item><item><title>Automating Building in Public</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/automating-building-in-public/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/automating-building-in-public/</guid><description>Introduction As I mentioned in my previous post, I have begun building my personal site to post projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been learning about &amp;ldquo;Building in Public&amp;rdquo; and central to it is to maintain constant communication with the public. I thought that it would be great if I could post links to my personal site on Twitter. That way my followers could instantly see any new updates I&amp;rsquo;ve made.</description></item><item><title>My New Site</title><link>https://hworden.github.io/posts/my-new-site/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hworden.github.io/posts/my-new-site/</guid><description>Intro Hi everyone, this is my first post on my new site. So welcome! I was able to build this site in less than an hour using Hugo.
Hugo Summary For those who may not know, Hugo is a static site generator. You can store your site content in markdown files, and then apply either a custom or open source theme to your site. Hugo will then take the content files, and translate them to equivalent html pages.</description></item></channel></rss>